RG 002:025, Judiciary Committee
Connecticut State Library
Judiciary Committee records
1981-2006
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Judiciary Committee
7.5 cubic feet
Judiciary Committee meeting files.
RG002_025_JUD
Multiple
Scope and Content
These records contain primarily meeting files.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Judiciary Committee
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Judiciary Committee -- Records and correspondence; Judges -- Selection and appointment -- Connecticut; Legislative bodies -- Public meetings -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas; Membership lists; Minutes; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession T003071, 1983-1985
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 9)
- Accession 1993-125, 1987-1990
  - Office of Legislative Management reports to Judiciary Committee, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Office of Legislative Management report on HB 8145 (1975) (Box 1)
  - Juvenile Justice System Combating Juvenile Drug Problem Task Force meeting minutes, agenda, reports, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Joiunt Favorable master list (Senate and House), 1990 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, raised bills, votes on judges, 1990 (Box 1)
- Accession 1998-013, 1985-1998
  - Subcommittee to Study State's Judicial Department meeting minutes, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, agendas, attendance, 1989-1994 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, agendas, attendance, 1985-1987 (Box 2)
  - Raising of bills, nominations, meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Public hearing and attendance, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Meeting minutes, Joint Favorable Reports, Review Claims, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Member list, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1998 (Box 3)
- Accession 1998-022, 1985
  - Meeting minutes, agenda, 1985 (Box 1)
- Accession 1998-024, 1981
  - Condominium Conversion Study, 1981 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-020, 1985-1986
  - Tort reform correspondence and reports, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-053, 1995
  - Meeting minutes, agendas, attendance, correspondence and copies of proposed bills, 1995 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-071, 1982
  - Transcript of committee meeting, 1982 August 17 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-072, 1991
  - Meeting minutes, member lists, House and Senate master list, 1991 (Box 1)
- Accession 1999-158, 1989-1997
  - Votes on judge nominations, raised bills, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Public hearings on judge nominations and workmen's comp, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Judge nominations, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Raised bills for 1992 Session, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Joint favorable bills, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Attendance, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bills referred from floor, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Agenda, meeting minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Judge nominations, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Bill record, 1992 (Box 1)
- Accession 2001-044, 1988-1998
  - Attendance public hearings, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - "Hate crimes" testimony, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Attendance public hearings, 1993 (Box 1)
  - State mandates, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Probate Court reform, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Meetings, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Meetings, 1995 (Box 1)
  - List of members and speakers, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Attendance public hearings, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Raised bills, 1997 Jan 13 (Box 1)
  - Meeting and hearing attendance, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Meetings, 1998 (Box 1)
- Accession 2007-049, 2005
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2005 April (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 2005 May-June (Box 2)
- Accession 2008-011, 2006
  - Meeting minutes, agendas, attendance, vote tally sheets, 2006 February-June (Box 1)